

### DETAILS

50182721

jesquivelnava@gmal.com

github.com/2JN

## LENGUAGES

English

Spanish

#### ★ SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Reactis
- Nodejs
- Python
- Php
- Laravel
- MySql
- MongoDB
- Git
- Wordpress
- CSS
- Linux / Unix

# **JONATHAN ESQUIVEL**

Software Developer

## PROFILE

Web developer and technology enthusiast, passionate to learn and create solutions for the modern days. I am a Full Stack Javascript developer, experienced in the creation of web applications through TDD. I also have great communication skills to share ideas and comments.

## EDUCATION

Universidad Marino Gálvez, Quetzaltenango – Guatemala January 2010 – November 2017

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Customer Respresentative at Telus Internation, Quetzaltenango – Guatemala

November 2017 – August 2018

Software Developer at Ciancoders, Quetzaltenango – Guatemala

August 2018 - April 2020

I have worked developing mostly web applications focusing for web e-commerce, as well ash hybrid desktop applications for commercial flight simulations and other specif platforms fo IoT using image recognition.

## PORFOLIO

#### **Transport Project:**

Project to schedule rides, that shows the route of the ride based on the user pick up point and drop off point, and shows the price of the ride. Created with ReactJS, Redux, Google maps API, Nodejs, Feathersjs and Authorize.net to handle payment transactions.

#### Flight Simulator:

Desktop application that connects with a flight simulator and show the sadistics of the airship. Build with electron, ReactJS, Redux

#### **Coffee Shop:**

Web page to buy and sell coffee. Made with React, Redux, Python and Django

#### Dr.Go

Mobile App that connects medics and patients. Patients can review a medic's expertise and contact them with ease. It also provides tools like prescriptions reminders, so medics can bring a better experience to their patients. Build with Ionic, Angular, Django, Python